Have you
finished that book?
I finished the first volume
and want to read the second.
But we can read it together.
I'll read it with you from the beginning.
Fried Rice Cakes
BBQ & Dumplings
Hi.
Qingqing, you're here. Have a seat.
I'll have a bowl of Wanza noodles
and a half portion
of wontons in chili oil.
Plus a duck head and a duck foot, right?
Exactly.
Alright. Take a seat,
it'll be ready in a minute.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
These Chongqing noodles
are the most authentic.
They're fragrant, numbing, and spicy.
And these wontons have thin wrappers
and generous fillings.
Try them.
Delicious, right?
This is my hidden gem.
I don't just tell anyone about it.
It's really good.
What should we have for lunch today?
I'm getting tired of the cafeteria's
spicy hot pot. How about we...
Qingqing,
look!
The genius from the math department.
No, I gotta practice my combos.
You broke my combo.
Can you put
this tireless energy
into something else?
Like studying?
Like chasing guys.
Now that 2847 is gone,
I have to carry on his legacy
and strive for the top
of the national server.
For us,
it's about spiritual enjoyment.
You wouldn't understand.
You think I don't understand?
You just don't.
Just like that, a captivating smile,
unforgettable at first sight.
Qingqing,
I got this
jasmine green milk tea
from a new shop near our school.
30% sugar, no ice, with boba.
Your favorite.
Thank you.
Jialing,
I got this for you.
Grape Four Seasons Spring tea.
And mine.
Thanks.
I guess I'm benefiting from Qingqing.
Impressive, Zhang Yi.
You know Qingqing so well.
Didn't we just
mention yesterday we wanted to try
this new shop?
And you brought it over today.
It was just a guess.
I saw a lot of girls lining up there.
I just knew you'd love it.
Are you interested in our Qingqing?
Who was the guy
that gave you milk tea today?
Do you already have a boyfriend?
How could I keep
such a good thing all to myself?
I'll forward it
to Tang Jialing right away.
Besties share the good stuff.
What do you think of me?
I love it so much. It's wonderful.
We women need to see things like this
to have the energy to make a living.
I'm so sorry.
My bestie sent this to me,
and I accidentally forwarded it to you.
I'm a decent person.
I never watch these things.
I was just about to criticize
this kind of behavior.
There's nothing to see here.
You should close it too.
I have them too,
and they're no worse than theirs.
Do you want to see?
Look,
Star Remains has
a new relationship system.
Players can form various relationships,
like lovers or best friends.
And the rewards are really rich.
What do you say?
Wanna log back in?
Reaching level five in a romance
gives you an outfit.
It's so pretty!
Why don't we become a couple
and do quests together?
Do you know what this romance entails?
I do.
I've researched it thoroughly.
We have to do daily events together,
take photos, form a pact,
invite friends for blessings, and stuff.
I heard we'll build
and decorate a house together later.
There might even be an option
to have kids.
You are my first...
First what?
First love?
You're my first too.
One last piece,
and the puzzle is complete.
Can I make a wish in advance?
What's your wish?
I want to meet you.
Okay, let's meet then.
Qingqing,
the market is having a sale tomorrow.
We'll head over there
first thing in the morning.
I must get that coat,
the best value of the year.
I'm meeting 2847 tomorrow.
Under the 28th tree,
where I put the first puzzle piece.
You're actually serious.
I thought you were joking.
What's wrong? Let me see.
Sister,
he's calling you sister.
This year's tea is hitting the market.
This is our tea garden.
Do you need
to buy some?
Our tea garden is the best in this estate.
I'd be thrilled if you could buy some.
Isn't this a classic pig-butchering scam?
Now he's asking you to buy tea.
So this 2847 has been fattening you up
for the slaughter.
After stringing you along for so long,
he's finally going in for the kill.
A pig-butchering scam?
Me?
Yeah.
Is this guy
super good at the game,
but constantly facing
setbacks in real life?
I entered a competition
and failed miserably.
Math is a game for geniuses.
And then he needs someone like you,
an ignorant, pure, and naive girl
to comfort him, save him,
and help him rebuild his confidence.
It gives you
a sense of accomplishment,
like you've saved a broken man.
Then he'll ask you to fund him
and help him make a comeback.
Now that you mention it,
it really seems like it.
But if he's playing with my feelings,
why is he in such a hurry to meet me?
You're meeting tomorrow, right?
And he asked you to buy tea today.
Which means...
It means he's most likely an ugly guy.
Afraid the offline meeting
will be a disaster.
Afraid you'll be completely
disappointed in him.
And then...
he won't be able to fleece
a little piggy like you anymore.
Qingqing,
this isn't your fault.
You're just too innocent and kind,
which is why those filthy scammers
always target you.
They can play with my feelings,
but not my money.
I guess I just trusted the wrong person.
Cancel.
Xinghai has been uninstalled.
From now on,
I'm quitting the game
and staying off the internet.
Where are you?
Do you need me to pick you up?
Shen,
why did your little romance
announce her relationship with my junior?
They are classmates, right?
I heard from my junior
that he's been chasing her
for a long time.
I'm sorry, Qingqing.
I was young
and ignorant back then.
My parents said they'd give me
pocket money if I sold tea.
So I mass-messaged everyone.
I not only used my smartwatch
but also my brother's phone.
I just wanted to earn some pocket money.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's good
that the misunderstanding is cleared up.
It's not a big deal.
Look, you're crying like a little cat.
Go wash your face.
Go on.
Go ahead.
You just deleted me
and wouldn't listen to my explanation.
Is that not a big deal either?
There were too many
telecom scams back then.
I was just being cautious.
If others knew
I chatted with a scammer for so long
and almost fell for it,
it would be really embarrassing.
Yun Qingqing,
you said you wanted to be
my romance back then...
Are you just messing with me?